websaver.ca 2019-02-07

# webSaver.ca - Canadian Coupons and Printable Coupons

## PRIVACY POLICY 

At webSaver.ca, we’re serious about protecting your privacy. The following policy details how we will use your personal information.

#### INFORMATION COLLECTED AND HOW WE USE IT:

You always remain in control of the information you provide to webSaver.ca. We collect two types of information about visitors: Personal information (such as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, etc.), which you have voluntarily submitted to us, and Aggregate information (such as information about how many visitors log on to our sites, the pages they access, how and where our coupons and/or offers are redeemed, etc.). A 2nd barcode is used to identify at which retailer you redeemed your coupons.

In general, while you can visit our website and add webSaver.ca to your shopping cart without telling us who you are or revealing personal information about yourself, you must register to create a profile or login in order to complete your order and receive your webSaver.ca offers. We collect, maintain and use personal information you have voluntarily submitted to process, mail, email, digitally notify or print your webSaver.ca coupons and/or offers (including those from partner and/or affiliate marketers), contact you, including via e­mail or digital notification to respond to your comments or requests for information. We will also use it to communicate with you about the webSaver.ca service in general, and send any weekly or daily newsletters you’ve subscribed to, as well as sponsored and/or special offers vial mail, email or digital advertising on behalf of carefully selected partners in regards to offers, promotions, and new products that may be of interest to you, unless you choose to opt out of these mailings. You can do this by changing your preferences on your profile page and/or clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any webSaver.ca e­mail. In addition, we may use personal information to provide you the most helpful and targeted products and services to meet your needs and respond to your inquiries.

Any contact with our customer service team may be recorded to help us provide better service.

#### DATA SHARING AND TRANSFER:

webSaver.ca will not, without your consent, trade, sell or share your personal information for use by any business, other than the ones to which you submitted your information, , unless required by law or as disclosed to you when the information is collected. If you do provide us with consent to share your information with other companies, we may share your information with companies who offer products and services that may be of interest to you. These companies may then contact you directly with product or sample offers, personalized offers and information, or to ask for your feedback on products and programs that they think may be of interest to you.

Your personal information will generally be stored in the webSaver.ca databases, which are located in Canada. Specific information is provided on the web site's consent or registration form, where needed.

#### COOKIES:

Cookies help us in many ways to make your visit to our website more enjoyable and meaningful to you. Cookies are text information files that your web browser places on your computer when you visit a website. webSaver.ca may use such "cookie" technology to obtain non-personal information from you as an online visitor. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but can be configured not to accept them or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. webSaver.ca may also use so-called "web beacons" to access the information contained in its cookies within the network of the webSaver.ca websites and interactive banner ads. 

#### YOU CAN CHOOSE TO BE CONTACTED OR NOT:

Our site allows you to choose, for example, to receive or stop receiving communications from us. If you would like to be removed from webSaver.ca programs you enrolled in or prevent further use of your personal information, please click here.

To Prevent Further Use of Your Personal Information - You will be provided with a way to remove yourself from webSaver.ca’s online programs.

#### CHILDREN'S PRIVACY:

We take care to protect children's privacy, and abide by national and international laws and regulations on children's privacy. 

#### SECURITY:

We take steps to make all information received from you online as secure as reasonably possible against unauthorized access and use.

#### ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION AND COMPLAINTS:

We attempt to keep your files complete, up-to-date, and accurate. You can conveniently access and modify your personal information though your profile. Change your username.

We are committed to working with you to obtain a fair and rapid resolution of any complaints or disputes about privacy. Questions regarding our Privacy Statement should be directed to webSaver.ca inquiries.

#### LINKS TO OTHER SITES:

webSaver.ca may contain links to other websites. webSaver.ca has no control over the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We recommend you carefully read the privacy policies of each site you visit. 

#### YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF OUR PRIVACY PRACTICE:

By using this website or any other webSaver.ca interactive banner ads, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Statement, and you adhere to the terms and conditions posted on the website.

#### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY:

webSaver.ca may update or modify this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary e-mail address you provided us during registration or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

#### HOW TO CONTACT US:

webSaver.ca is committed to working with consumers to obtain a fair and rapid resolution of any complaints or disputes about privacy. Please send us your questions or comments regarding our privacy practices. 

webSaver.ca  
4810 Jean-Talon St. W,  
Suite 203, Montréal, Québec,  
Canada H4P 2N5  
Date of Last Revision: February 7, 2019  

×

Hey webSaver!  
It seems you're trying to access our site using IE 8, a browser we no longer support.  
For a better experience, please try accessing the site using another browser such as Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox or Safari or update your internet explorer to the latest version.

Close

×

If you want these coupons please checkout now, otherwise they will be removed from your shopping cart.

Skip [Check Out]()
